Guide to the Jonathan Edwards Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Writings of Jonathan Edwards, c. 1720-84; Series I; 10.3; (21 boxes)
  - SERMONS
    - LUKE 15:15-16: "The devil is a cruel master" (p. 1), 1742 Nov (Box 8, Folder 576)
    - LUKE 15:16-20: "Obs. 1. That which natural persons set their hearts upon and depend upon for happiness is not the food of children or the bread of men but the food of swine..." (p. 3), 1741 Aug (Box 8, Folder 577)
    - LUKE 15:18-19: "When persons reflect on the greatness of their sins the improvement they should make of it should not be to discourage 'em but to humble 'em" (p. 2), 1734 Aug (Box 8, Folder 578)
    - LUKE 15:22: "A truly penitent sinner has the best righteousness that ever any creature appeared in" (p. 3), 1739/40 Jan (Box 8, Folder 579)
    - LUKE 15:28-31: "Prop. I. Persons that have been long religious are oftentimes much displeased that God shews mercy to others that have lived wicked lives and but lately begun in religion" (p. 7), three[?] sermons, 1735 Apr (Box 8, Folder 580)
    - LUKE 16:8-9: "We ought to shew ourselves as wise for our spiritual and eternal interest as worldly minded men are wont to do for their temporal interest" (p. 17), two sermons, 1736, 1754 (Box 8, Folder 581)
    - LUKE 16:10-12: "If God should give heaven to an ungodly man he would improve it in the service of his lusts" (p. 6), 1737, 1755 (Box 8, Folder 582)
    - LUKE 16:15: "Tis very frequently and commonly so that those things that are highly esteemed amongst men are abominable in the sight of God" (p. 4), 1736/7 Feb (Box 8, Folder 583)
    - LUKE 16:16: "It concerns everyone that would obtain the kingdom of God to be pressing into it" (p. 4), 1735 Feb (Box 8, Folder 584)
    - LUKE 16:19: "1. God is as willing to shew mercy to one nation as another if they repent to turn to him" (p. 1), 1753 Jun
      See: Box 14, folder 1071
    - LUKE 16:22-23: "When men die their souls do immediately go to heaven or to hell" (p. 8), 1744 Sep (Box 8, Folder 585)
    - LUKE 16:22-23: "That which I intend to speak of at this time from this text is the punishment of wicked men in hell after death" (p. 1), 1751 Jul
      See: Box 14, folder 1072
    - LUKE 16:23: "The wicked will hereafter see the saints in their glory and blessedness afar off" (p. 1), 1746, 1751 (Box 8, Folder 586)
      "1746 Lecture"
    - LUKE 16:24: "That the torments of hell are exceeding great" (p. 5), n.d. (Box 8, Folder 587)
    - LUKE 16:25: "I. Wicked men in hell will remember how things were with them here in this world" (p. 3), 1757, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 588)
    - LUKE 16:25: "II. The wicked in hell will be sensible what a happy state the saints are in [in] heaven" (p. 2), [1757], n.d (Box 8, Folder 589)
    - LUKE 16:27-28: "When [men] come into another world, they will have their eyes opened and will see better than they do now the things they had been taught in this world", 1756 May
      See: Box 14, folder 1073
      "At Stockbridge"
    - LUKE 17:9: "That God don't thank men for doing those things which he commands them" (p. 2) (Box 8, Folder 590)
    - LUKE 17:32: "We ought not to look back when we are flying out of Sodom" (p. 3), 1735 May (Box 8, Folder 591)
    - LUKE 18:1: "I. What is prayer. II. All men ought to pray to God... III. Pray always... IV. What we should pray for" (pp. 1-7), 1753 May
      See: Box 14, folder 1074
    - LUKE 18:13: "Now therefore you, if ever you obtain the favor of God, must do it as this man [the publican] did" (p. 1), 1750/1, 1752
      See: Box 14, folder 1075
    - LUKE 18:14: "A self-righteous spirit, or a disposition to trust in a man's own righteousness, is abominable unto God" (p. 5), 1736 Nov (Box 8, Folder 592)
    - LUKE 18:38-39: "Sinners that meet with opposition and discouragements in their seeking mercy should be as it were willful and obstinate in it that they will seek mercy" (p. 3), 1741 Apr (Box 8, Folder 593)
    - LUKE 19:8-9: "The making restitution wherein persons have injured others in their outward estates is a duty of great importance and necessity to professing converts in order to any proper evidence of the truth of their conversion" (p. 4), 1746 May (Box 8, Folder 594)
    - LUKE 19:10: "I would shew, 1. Whence Christ came. 2. Whither he came. 3. Those that he came for the sake of were poor lost creatures. 4. That he came to seek them, and 5. That he seeks them to that end that he may save them" (p. 4), 1741 Jun (Box 8, Folder 595)
    - LUKE 19:10: "What is meant is that he [the Son of man] came into the world to seek and save sinners" (p. 1), 1751 Jun
      See: Box 14, folder 1076
    - LUKE 19:40: "Those persons that are unaffected with the great and glorious things of the gospel have hearts harder than the very stones" (p. 5), 1736 Mar (Box 8, Folder 596)
    - LUKE 19:41: "II. To give the reasons why Christ wept over Jerusalem 1. He knew that the greater part of the inhabitants were in a graceless unconverted state (p. 9) "2. He knew the greatness of the misery of such a state" (p. 10) 3. "...that the sinners of that city were in a distinguishingly deplorable state" (p. 11), 1741, 1751 (Box 8, Folder 597)
      "Cold Spring, at Canaan, Springfield, Stockbridge, Boston, Ipswich Hamlet"
    - LUKE 19:42: "That if sinners outstand their day of grace they will surely perish" (p. 4) (Box 8, Folder 598)
    - LUKE 19:42: Two propositions: "I. If ever those that are in a special manner far from conversion are converted, tis most likely to be at a time when Christ is extraordinarily present..." (p. 2), 1741 Jun (Box 8, Folder 599)
    - LUKE 21:36: "I. Many dreadful things are coming upon this world. II. The righteous and they only shall be thought fit to [?] those things that shall come" (p. 1), [1758 Jan 15]
      See: Box 14, folder 1077
    - LUKE 22:19: "The Lord's Supper ought to be kept up and attended in remembrance of Christ" (p. 3), 1734 Jun (Box 8, Folder 600)
      "Sacrament"
    - LUKE 22:27: "Christians are entertained at a table at which they feast and Christ serves" (p. 1), 1742 Nov (Box 8, Folder 601)
    - LUKE 22:31: "That Christ's intercession is that which will effectually secure believers from ever totally and finally falling away from grace" (p. 3) (Box 8, Folder 602)
    - LUKE 22:32: "Those that have true grace in their hearts may yet stand in great need of being converted" (p. 3), two sermons, 1740 Aug (Box 8, Folder 603)
    - LUKE 22:44: "That which I shall make the subject of my present discourse is Christ's agony" (p. 3), 1739, 1757 (Box 8, Folder 604)
    - LUKE 22:48: "That there are those that make an outward shew of friendship to Jesus Christ that at the same time act the part of enemies and betrayers" (p. 3) (Box 8, Folder 605)
    - LUKE 24:47: "In speaking from this text I would 1. Shew you what true repentance is..." (p. 1), 1751 Oct
      See: Box 14, folder 1078
    - LUKE 24:32: "Tis a common [thing] with the saints that their hearts do burn within them while divine things are represented to them" (p. 4), 1736, 1755 (Box 8, Folder 606)
    - JOHN 1:10-11: "I shall shew how the case was with them with respect to Christ's appearance among them in those days and their not knowing or receiving him, and 2. shall make application...to our own case..." (p. 2), 1741 Jul (Box 8, Folder 607)
    - JOHN 1:12: "Good men whose hearts receive Jesus Christ are God's children" (p. 1), 1750/1, 1752
      See: Box 14, folder 1079
    - JOHN 1:12-13: "I. How true believers receive Christ... II. How God gives such as receive Christ the privileges of his children" (p. 1), 1755
      See: Box 14, folder 1080
    - JOHN 1:14: "That our Lord Jesus Christ is full of grace and truth", 1752, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 608-609)
      In shorthand on one, in longhand on the other: "Preached the second time at a private meeting"
    - JOHN 1:16: "That believers do receive of Christ, of the benediction he himself hath, and do partake with him therein. 2. That there is every grace in the heart of a believer which there is in Jesus Christ himself" (p. 1), 1752, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 610)
    - JOHN 1:29: "1. How that Christ is like a lamb. 2. That he is the Lamb that takes away the sin of the world. 3. That we should look upon and behold this Lamb of God" (p. 1), 1750 Feb
      See: Box 14, folder 1081
    - JOHN 1:41-2: "When persons have truly come to Christ themselves they naturally desire to bring others also to him" (p. 5), 1733 Dec (Box 8, Folder 611)
    - JOHN 1:46: "Should come to Christ and give your hearts to Christ" (p. 1), 1752 Dec
      See: Box 14, folder 1082
    - JOHN 1:47: "Tis a great thing to be indeed a converted person" (p. 4), three preaching units, 1739 Sep (Box 8, Folder 612)
    - JOHN 3:3: "Except a man be born again he cannot see the kingdom of God" (p. 1), 1753, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 613)
    - JOHN 3:7: "Tis no wonder that Christ said that we must be born again" (p. 4), 1739/40 Jan (Box 8, Folder 614)
    - JOHN 3:8: "God is sovereign in the work of conversion" (p. 1), 1734 Dec (Box 8, Folder 615)
      "This has been preached at New Place"
    - JOHN 3:10-11: "There is such a thing as conversion" (p. 2), 1740 Jul (Box 8, Folder 616)
    - JOHN 3:16: "There is an answerableness between the greatness of the misery of hell and the happiness of heaven, and the greatness of the things that have been done that sinners might be saved from hell and might obtain heaven" (p. 4) (Box 8, Folder 617)
    - JOHN 3:36: "Unless persons believe in Jesus Christ they shall not see eternal life" (p. 3), 1734, 1755 (Box 8, Folder 618)
    - JOHN 3:36: "He that don't believe on the Lord Jesus Christ, the wrath of God abideth on him" (p. 1), 1734, 1755 (Box 8, Folder 619)
    - JOHN 5:43: "Man's heart is naturally wholly opposite to the gospel" (p. 3), 1733 Jun (Box 8, Folder 620)
    - JOHN 5:45: "The law which natural men trust in to justify them will only condemn 'em" (p. 4), 1741 Apr (Box 8, Folder 621)
    - JOHN 6:33: "Christ is the bread of God" (p. 1), 1748/9 Feb (Box 8, Folder 622)
    - JOHN 6:45: "There never was any man that once came to understand what manner of One Christ was but his heart was infallibly drawn to Him" (p. 4), 1740 Oct (Box 8, Folder 623)
    - JOHN 6:51: "All divine blessings are as much in and through Christ as if they were a feast provided of his flesh that was given for us" (p. 1), 1749 Jun (Box 8, Folder 624)
    - JOHN 6:68: "It is by Christ alone that eternal life is ever communicated to men" (p. 3), n.d.
      See: Box 14, folder 1083
    - JOHN 7:18: "Men in the exercise of true religion do make God and not themselves their highest end; or, men in the exercises of true religion do ultimately seek God and not themselves" (p. 3), 1745 Mar (Box 8, Folder 625)
    - JOHN 7:34: "Some men seek salvation and never obtain it" (p. 1), 1752 Apr
      See: Box 14, folder 1084
    - JOHN 7:37: "In these words ["If any man thirst, let him come unto me"] we have one of the most noted invitations of the gospel..." (p. 1), 1748 Oct (Box 8, Folder 626)
    - JOHN 8:12: "That Jesus Christ is the light of the world. We propose thus to handle this doctrine, 1. To shew how the world is in darkness without Christ 2. How it is enlightened by him. 3. To shew by what means Christ communicates his light" (p. 3)
      See: Box 14, folder 1085
    - JOHN 8:12: "Light and life do accompany each other in the Lord Jesus Christ" (p.1), 1741/2 Jan (Box 8, Folder 627)
    - JOHN 8:34: "That wicked men are servants and slaves to sin" (p. 3)
      See: Box 14, folder 1086
    - JOHN 8:44: "That wicked men are the children of the devil" (p. 3), n.d. (Box 8, Folder 628)
    - JOHN 8:44: "The devil is a liar" (p. 3), 1736 Mar (Box 8, Folder 629)
    - JOHN 10:4: "There is a sweet harmony between Christ and the soul of the true Christian" (p. 5), 1735 Aug (Box 8, Folder 630)
    - JOHN 10:9: "Christ is the door by which men enter into a state of salvation, liberty and satisfaction" (p. 1), 1749 Aug (Box 8, Folder 631)
    - JOHN 10:18: "Christ was voluntary in subjecting himself to those sufferings that he underwent" (p. 3), 1736 Apr (Box 8, Folder 632)
    - JOHN 10:27: "Hear Christ's voice. Understand. Believe. Obey" (p. 1), 1754 Jul
      See: Box 14, folder 1087
    - JOHN 10:37-38: "The miracles that Christ wrought when he was here upon earth were divine works" (p. 3), two lectures, 1739/40-56 (Box 8, Folder 633)
    - JOHN 12:32: "...in an use of exhortation. I. Call upon and exhort all that are in natural condition even at this time to turn from their sins to God..." (p. 1) (Box 8, Folder 634)
    - JOHN 12:32: "III. I would apply this to such as have an interest in the L.J.X.", n.d. (Box 8, Folder 635)
    - JOHN 12:32: Fragment, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 636)
    - JOHN 13:23: "Christ stands ready graciously to admit those that come to him as disciples to the utmost freedom of access and intimacy to communion" (p. 4), 1736/7 Jan (Box 8, Folder 637)
    - JOHN 13:30: "Christ oftentimes gives those professing Christianity that ben't true disciples that which is agreeable to their carnal hearts and sends 'em away with it" (p. 1), 1742 Jun (Box 8, Folder 638)
    - JOHN 14:2: "Jesus Christ has dealt faithfully with us and has plainly told us the truth in all things that concern our welfare," two or more sermons, 1734 Mar (Box 8, Folder 639)
    - JOHN 14:2: "There are two propositions contained in the words, viz. I. That heaven is God's house, and II. that in this house of God there are many mansions" (p. 3), 1737 Dec 25 (Box 8, Folder 640)
      "The sabbath after the seating the new meeting house"
    - JOHN 14:7: "True saints differ from all the world in that they know and receive the Spirit of God and have him dwelling in their hearts" (p. 1), 1746 Jul (Box 9, Folder 641)
    - JOHN 14:23: "They that love and obey Christ, God and Christ will come to them and dwell with them" (p. 3), two sermons, 1733-55 (Box 9, Folder 642)
    - JOHN 14:27: "That peace which Christ when he died left as a legacy to all his true saints, is very diverse from all those things which the men of this world bequeath to their children" (p. 2), [prob. 1750-53] (Box 9, Folder 643)
      "Preached at Canaan"
    - JOHN 15:5: "That Christ Jesus is the original and fountain of all spiritual life and nourishment" (p. 2)
      See: Box 14, folder 1088
    - JOHN 15:5: "I. I would shew how Christ is the vine..." (p. 1), 1745 Mar (Box 9, Folder 644)
    - JOHN 15:5: "I. Christ [is] in [the] saints" (p. 1) "II. Believers are in Christ" (p. 5) "III. Those branches that are truly and vitally united to the true vine are fruitful branches" (p. 14) "IV. The way for Christians to be fruitful...is to cleave to Christ" (p. 31), 1745 Mar (Box 9, Folder 645)
    - JOHN 15:10: "That Jesus Christ kept all his Father's commandments" (p. 5), 1755, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 646)
    - JOHN 15:15: "When Christ was upon earth he did not keep at an awful distance from his disciples but was intimate with them as friends (p. 4), two sermons, 1733 Dec (Box 9, Folder 647)
    - JOHN 16:8: "That the work of the Holy Ghost as Christ's messenger is to convince men of sin, of righteousness and of judgment" (p. 3), seven sermons (Box 9, Folder 648)
    - JOHN 18:7-9: "Obs. 1. Christ did not forget his disciples but was full of concern for their welfare in the time of his last sufferings" (p. 2), 1744 Sep (Box 9, Folder 649)
    - JOHN 21:5: "Christ has a tender concern and love for his people that they should be provided for and their wants supplied as a father has for his children" (p.2), 1739, 1751 (Box 9, Folder 650)
    - ACTS 1:9: "Subject: Christ's ascension into heaven" (p. 1), 1749 Apr (Box 9, Folder 651)
    - ACTS 1:25: "Observation: Judas Iscariot has been in hell for more than seventeen hundred years. In the doctrinal handling of this obs. I would take notice of several things..." (p. 1), 1742 Jul (Box 9, Folder 652)
    - ACTS 2:37: "Commonly sinners before they are converted and have their sins forgiven them are pricked and wounded in their heart" (p. 1), 1751 Nov
      See: Box 14, folder 1089
    - ACTS 3:15: "Jesus Christ is the Prince of life" (p. 2), 1751, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 653)
    - ACTS 3:22-23: "I. Christ is a great prophet. II. Made our brother. III. Ought to hear him" (p. 1), 1756 Apr
      See: Box 14, folder 1090
    - ACTS 4:11: "Unbelievers set nothing by all the glory and excellency that is in Christ" (p. 3), 1736, 1753 (Box 9, Folder 654)
    - ACTS 5:31: "The Lord Jesus Christ works salvation as a Prince" (p. 1), 1742, 1751 (Box 9, Folder 655)
    - ACTS 6:1-3: "That the main business of a deacon by Christ's appointments is to take care of the distribution of the church's charity for the outward supply of those that need" (p. 7), 1739 Jun (Box 9, Folder 656)
    - ACTS 6:15: "A great fulness of the pure influences of the Spirit of God joined with discretion will make a person appear and behave with that heavenly amiableness, that his face will be beheld as it were like the face of an angel" (p. 1), [ca. 1741-42?] (Box 9, Folder 657)
    - ACTS 7:51: "Tis a great sin to resist the Spirit of God" (p. 3), 1735 Apr (Box 9, Folder 658)
    - ACTS 8:8: "Tis a blessed time amongst a people when is is a time of the pouring out of God's Spirit upon them" (p. 3), n.d. (Box 9, Folder 659)
    - ACTS 8:20-22: "A man may eternally undo himself in one thought of his heart" (p. 3), 1736 Jun (Box 9, Folder 660)
    - ACTS 8:21: "When the Spirit of God has been remarkably poured out in his converting and saving influences on a people, tis an awful thing to dwell among them and yet have no part nor lot in the matter" (p. 2), 1735 Aug (Box 9, Folder 661)
    - ACTS 8:22: "That particular repentance is necessary to salvation" (p. 4), n.d. (Box 9, Folder 662)
    - ACTS 8:23: "...in the gall of bitterness" [Text:] "I. I shall shew what is the proper meaning of the phrase. II. How the phrase is applicable to all unconverted persons" (p. 1), 1741 Jul (Box 9, Folder 663)
    - ACTS 9:13-15: "Tis so with respect to God's bestowment of saving mercy on some persons, that there is no other account to be given of it but that he will shew mercy" (p. 4), 1738/9 Feb (Box 9, Folder 664)
    - ACTS 10:4-6: "To be much in deeds of charity is the way to have spiritual discoveries" (p. 3), 1740/1 (Box 9, Folder 665)
    - ACTS 11:12-13: "Now I am come to preach the true religion to you and to your children as Peter did to Cornelius and his family, that you and all your children may be saved... Now therefore I'll tell you what true religion is..." (p. 3), 1750/1 Jan
      See: Box 14, folder 1091
      Apparently first sermon to the Indians, preached to Stockbridge Indians and Mohawks
    - ACTS 13:41: "The aggravated misery of many unbelievers appears in that though they hear and see much of God's wonderful work of salvation yet they never believe but despise and wonder and perish" (p. 5), 1737 Mar 13 (Box 9, Folder 666)
    - ACTS 14:23: "The solemn setting apart of one to the work and office of a gospel minister is an affair wherein God should earnestly be sought" (p. 3), 1740/1 Jan (Box 9, Folder 667)
      Fast at Hadley[?] preceding ordination
    - ACTS 14:26-27: "Tis a special and glorious work of God to open the way for the propagation of the gospel among the heathen" (p. 1), 1753 May
      See: Box 14, folder 1092
      "Private meeting on the occasion of Messrs. W___gis[?] and Hawley's going into the country of the six nations"
    - ACTS 16:9: "This may teach you how great your calamity was before you had the gospel preached and what cause of thankfulness" (p. 8), 1751 Aug
      See: Box 14, folder 1093
      "Fast before installment," preached to Stockbridge Indians and Mohawks
    - ACTS 16:29-30: "They that are in a natural condition, are in a dreadful condition" (p. 3), 1734 Aug (Box 9, Folder 668)
    - ACTS 16:29-31: "Sinners under concern and distress of mind about the condition of their souls ought to take encouragement from the infinite mercy of God in Christ" (p. 5), 1733/4 Feb (Box 9, Folder 669)
    - ACTS 16:29-31: "I. They that are not converted are in a dreadful condition II. That is a thing that men should be greatly concerned about, to know what they shall do to be save" (p. 1), 1753 Feb
      See: Box 14, folder 1094
    - ACTS 16:30: "Tis of exceeding great importance and what men had need to be greatly concerned about that they should be saved" (p. 1), 1755 Aug
      See: Box 14, folder 1095
    - ACTS 17:11: "That it is true nobleness of mind readily and sincerely to entertain Christianity" (p. 3) (Box 9, Folder 670)
    - ACTS 17:30: "I would speak from these words: 1. By shewing what is meant by repenting in the words. 2. By shewing how they were true of those days...3. By shewing how they are applicable to these days, and 4. By giving agreeable exhortations unto those that are in this congregation" (p. 1), 1741 Aug (Box 9, Folder 671)
    - ACTS 17:31: "God hath appointed a day in which he will judge the world in righteousness by Jesus Christ" (p. 4), n.d. (Box 9, Folder 672)
    - ACTS 19:19: "When the Spirit of God has been remarkably poured out on a people, a thorough reformation of those things that before were amiss amongst them ought to be the effect of it" (p. 7), 1736 Apr 1 (Box 9, Folder 673)
      "Fast day"
    - ACTS 20:24: "Tis a thing that greatly concerns the professors of religion, that they should finish their course with joy" (p. 1), 1744, 1757 (Box 9, Folder 674)
    - ACTS 20:28: "The church of God is purchased by the blood of God", 1745 Dec (Box 9, Folder 675)
    - ACTS 20:28: "My design from these words is to consider Christ's expending his own blood for the salvation and happiness of the souls of men, in the view both of an inducement and a direction to ministers to exert themselves for the same end" (p. 4), 1754, 1756 (Box 9, Folder 676)
      "Prepared for the installment of Mr. Billing March 28, 1754" "Preached also at N. 3 at Mr. Jones's ordination"
    - ACTS 24:25: "Subject: sinners delaying and putting off the great concern of their souls til a supposed more convenient season" (p. 1), 1749, 1752 (Box 9, Folder 677)
    - ACTS 26:18: "In saving conversion they that are blind and in darkness have their eyes opened and are turned from darkness unto light" (p. 1), 1747 Nov (Box 9, Folder 678)
    - ACTS 26:18: "In saving conversion sinners are turned from the power of Satan unto God" (p. 1), 1747 Dec (Box 9, Folder 679)
    - ACTS 26:18: "When a sinner is converted his sins are forgiven" (p. 1), 1747 Dec (Box 9, Folder 680)
    - ACTS 26:18: "When a sinner is converted he has an inheritance given him among them that are sanctified" (p. 1), 1747 Dec (Box 9, Folder 681)
    - ROM. 1:20: "The being and attributes of God are clearly to be seen by the works of creation" (p. 1), 1743, 1756 (Box 9, Folder 682)
    - ROM. 1:21: "The subject, the great obligation we are under to be thankful to God for his goodness" (p. 1), 1751 Nov 7
      See: Box 14, folder 1096
      Thanksgiving sermon preached to Stockbridge Indians and Mohawks
    - ROM. 1:24: "God sometimes punishes sin by giving men up to sin" (p. 3), n.d.
      See: Box 14, folder 1097
    - ROM. 2:5: "Unawakened and impenitent sinners do heap up to themselves wrath against the day of wrath as men are wont to heap up treasures" (p. 4) (Box 9, Folder 683)
    - ROM. 2:5: "1. That the day of judgment is a day of wrath" (p. 1), [1741?] (Box 9, Folder 684)
    - ROM. 2:8-9: "Indignation, wrath, and misery and anguish of soul is the portion that God has allotted to wicked men" (p. 4), 1735 Nov (Box 9, Folder 685)
    - ROM 2:10: "Glory, honor, and peace is the portion that God has given to all the godly" (p. 2), [1735 Dec?] (Box 9, Folder 686)
    - ROM. 2:16: "The secrets of men must all come into judgement before God" (p. 3), n.d. (Box 9, Folder 687)